socialhoney.co 2016-11-03

# Social Honey

### Privacy Policy

This policy ("Privacy Policy") is applicable to all data and information collected through all websites and services, including software, (the "Service", "Services") operated or enabled by Social Honey Ltd. ("Social Honey", "we", "us", "our"), that relates to our users ("you", "your"). Please read the privacy policy to learn more. By visiting or using our websites or Services in any manner, you are acknowledging and accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, and consent that we collect, use and share your information in the ways outlined below.

#### What information do we collect?

Whenever you use our Services we, as well as third-party vendors may collect information about how the Services are being used. This is done through a variety of technologies and can be performed automatically or passively. When you use our websites, Services, or websites that use our Services, your browser sends data ("Log Data") that we record. The information collected may include, but is not limited to, browser information, device information, location information, url information, "cookie" information, and other normal HTTP request information. "Cookies" are text files that exist in your browser and are used as identifiers that recognize your browser or device, and tell us which pages you interact with. We also use "Local Storage" which is a feature of most modern web browsers, to store user identifiers and preferences. We use this information, which does not contain personal information, to analyze and build statistics about trends, usage of our Services, improve performance of our Services, and build anonymized aggregated data about user preferences. Additionally, we, and third party vendors, may use beacons and scripts to analyze user actions, "clicks" and movements throughout the website or with Services.

#### Information you provide to us

When signing up for our Services as a customer or otherwise communicating with us, we may ask you for Personal Information in the form of name, email address or phone number. If you do not want your Personal Information collected as a customer, please do not submit it. Customers are not permitted to collect Personal Information through the use of our Services.

#### Will this information be shared?

Beyond actions outlined in this Privacy Policy, we will not provide Personal Information to any non-Service related third party without first receiving your consent. We may share any non-personal information for example, usage information, demographic, or behavioural data with third parties. We may also join this non-personal information with other non-personal information for anonymized trend analysis.

We may employ other companies as "Trusted Third Parties" to supply services or functions in order to provide the Services to you on our behalf. These Trusted Third Parties do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share beyond what is necessary to support us.

We reserve the right to share any information, including Personal Information, that we reasonably believe required by law or to protect the safety and privacy of Social Honey, its customers and users.

#### Can I Opt-Out

Yes. We take great pride in providing personalized Services that do not infringe on the privacy of the individual. We do however understand that this type of information collection may be a concern to you. You can Opt-Out of our personalization Services, and also third party services.

**To Opt-Out of the Social Honey personalization Service click[here]()**   
Note, resetting your browser or clearing its cache will remove the Opt-Out settings for Social Honey's personalization Services and doing so will require you Opt-Out again.

**To Opt-Out of third party services you can block cookies from your web browser or manage your preferences with each individually. A good resource for this is available via the[Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) program**

If you are a customer and wish to have your Personal Information updated or removed, please contact us via email at info@socialhoney.co and we'll process the change within 10 days. Note that some Personal Information is required for the delivery of Services. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may make amendments to this Privacy Policy from time to time, and use of any and all information is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. If we make changes to the way we use Personal Information we will announce such change on our website before the change comes into effect. Please re-visit this site from time to time to ensure you are kept up to date with the most recent Privacy Policy changes.

Update Date: 14th June 2016

#### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns about privacy and information use please send us a detailed email to [info@socialhoney.co](mailto:info@socialhoney.co) and we'll make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Social Honey Ltd.  
3rd Floor, Embassy House  
Herbert Park Lane, Ballsbridge  
Dublin 4, Ireland
